simmonsfirst.com 2012-11-08

# Privacy Policy

Protecting your privacy is important to Simmons First. We believe the confidentiality and protection of customer information is one of our fundamental responsibilities. Simmons First is committed to providing our customers a broad range of financial products and services while safeguarding customer information. 

Simmons First's Privacy Policy describes how we protect the confidentiality of the personal financial information you share with us and the types of nonpublic, personal information collected and how the information is used. Nonpublic personal information is information we obtain in connection with providing a financial product or service to you. 

Simmons First's Privacy Policy applies to individuals who obtain or have obtained from us a financial product or service that is used primarily for personal, family or household purposes.

We will not disclose information about you to anyone except as disclosed in our Privacy Policy or as permitted by law.

** Click Here to view Simmons First's Notice Of Your Financial Rights **

**Click Here for Printable **Notice Of Your Financial Privacy Rights**  **

**ADDITIONAL WAYS TO MAKE YOUR BANKING WITH SIMMONS FIRST MORE SECURE**

_**FDIC Offers Identity Theft Help** _

View a multimedia presentation created by the FDIC, which provides information on steps consumers should take to secure their computer and protect themselves from identity theft, as well as what they should do if they are victimized by the crime. [>>>Click Here to view the Multimedia Presentation](http://www.fdic.gov/consumers/consumer/guard/index.html).

Note: Macromedia Flash Player is required to view this presentation. The latest version of Macromedia Flash Player can be downloaded at <http://www.macromedia.com/go/getflashplayer>.

_**Protect Yourself From Email Fraud** _

Typically, criminals send emails that look like they are from legitimate sources, but are not. The fake messages (Phishing) generally include a link to phony, or spoofed, websites where victims are asked to provide sensitive, personal information. The information goes to criminals, rather than the legitimate business. >>>For More Information Click Here

_**MasterCard SecureCode** _

The Security and Privacy of your payments are important. Protect your Simmons First MasterCard with your own personal password so only you can purchase with them online. It is easy safe and free of charge. [>>>Click Here To Register](https://secure4.arcot.com/vpas/simmons_vbvisa/enroll/index.jsp?locale=en_US&bankid=1053).

_**STOP Mortgage Fraud** _

Features to help you avoid becoming a victim of Mortgage fraud or abusive lending. [>>>Click Here To Learn More](http://www.stopfraud.gov/protect-mortgage.html).

_**True Credit** _

True Credit offers access to your personal credit information, credit monitoring for fraudulent activity, Identity Theft Insurance and more. [For More Information Click Here](http://www.truecredit.com/entry/trueCreditEntry.jsp).

_**Verified by VISA** _

With Verified by Visa service you can password protect purchases when shopping at participating merchants on the internet with your Simmons First Visa Card. Verified by Visa is a free service offered to all Credit Card Customers. [>>>Register now for added security when you use your Simmons First Credit Card online](https://secure4.arcot.com/vpas/simmons_vbvisa/enroll/index.jsp?locale=en_US&bankid=1053). 

_**Visa Security Sense** _

Visa Security Sense provides cardholders tips with practical know-how for protecting account information and resolving unauthorized card use. Highlights of the website include:

  * Tips for Preventing Fraud

  * Fraud News

  * Resources for Fighting Fraud

  * How Visa Protects You

Check out the site today at [www.visasecuritysense.com](http://www.visasecuritysense.com/)
